<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Study-groups on Zachary Feng</title>
    <link>https://zachary-feng.github.io/study-groups/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Study-groups on Zachary Feng</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zachary-feng.github.io/study-groups/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Global reciprocity study group</title>
      <link>https://zachary-feng.github.io/study-groups/global-reciprocity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zachary-feng.github.io/study-groups/global-reciprocity/</guid>
      <description>This is the homepage for the weekly study group on global Langlands reciprocity organized by Havard Damm-Johnsen and myself in Hilary Term 2024 at Oxford.
Schedule All talks will be held on Thursdays, 13.30 to 15.00 in C2. Please email me if you would like to be added to or removed from the current mailing list.
Week Number Topic Speaker Notes Week 2, Jan 25 GL(2)/Q weight 2 (Eichler-Shimura) Arun [Typed] Week 3, Feb 1 GL(2)/Q weight 1 (Deligne-Serre) Havard [Typed] Week 4, Feb 8 No talk Week 5, Feb 15 GL(2)/F real quadratic (Carayol) Alex TBD Week 6, Feb 22 TBD TBD TBD Week 7, Feb 29 TBD TBD TBD Week 8, Mar 7 TBD TBD TBD References The appendix by Brian Conrad, in Ribet and Stein, Lectures on Serre&amp;rsquo;s conjectures </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montreal functor study group</title>
      <link>https://zachary-feng.github.io/study-groups/montreal-functor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zachary-feng.github.io/study-groups/montreal-functor/</guid>
      <description>This is the homepage for the weekly study group on Colmez&amp;rsquo;s Montreal functor organized by Finn Wiersig, James Taylor and myself in Hilary Term 2024 at Oxford.
Schedule All talks will be held on Thursdays, 11.15 to 12.30 in C2. Please email me if you would like to be added to or removed from the current mailing list.
Week Number Topic Speaker Notes Week 2, Jan 25 mod p representations of GL2(Qp) Alex [Written] Week 3, Feb 1 mod p Galois reps; mod p LLC for GL2(Qp) Zach [Typed] [Written] Week 4, Feb 8 Banach space representations Mick [Written] Week 5, Feb 15 (phi,Gamma)-modules Arun TBD Week 6, Feb 22 Definition of the Montreal functor James T TBD Week 7, Feb 29 Properties of the Montreal functor Havard TBD Week 8, Mar 7 p-adic LLC for GL2(Qp) James N TBD References Laurent Berger, La correspondance de Langlands locale p-adique pour GL2(Qp) Gergely Jakovac, p-adic representations and the Montreal functor Vytautas Paskunas, The image of Colmez&amp;rsquo;s Montreal functor </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
